consumercourtforum.in 2013-12-25

# Privacy Policy

> * [www.consumercourtforum.in](http://www.consumercourtforum.in/) recognizes that you care about the personal information that is held about you and how that is used.
> 
> * This privacy policy applies to all personal data, submitted by you, to the [www.consumercourtforum.in](http://www.consumercourtforum.in/) web site.
> 
> * By registering to [www.consumercourtforum.in](http://www.consumercourtforum.in/) you need to submit a chosen name and contact information, more specifically an e-mail address. No extremely personal information, such as Social Security, pan card numbers or Credit Card numbers are stored by us.
> 
> * [www.consumercourtforum.in](http://www.consumercourtforum.in/) also stores and reads cookies to and from your computer. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our forums and general website features to recognize your browser for when you return to this web site. By using this website, you agree that both the webserver, and any trusted 3rd party we chose, such as advertising networks, may place a tracking cookie on your machine and access it at any time during your session. In general, cookies are safe and are not a security issue when being used from 'trusted' internet sites, such as [www.consumercourtforum.in](http://www.consumercourtforum.in/). For information on how to manage cookies in your browser, please visit AboutCookies.org
> 
> * [www.consumercourtforum.in](http://www.consumercourtforum.in/) will not sell, transmit or distribute any data held without your prior permission or consent, unless required to do so under relevant United States, United Kingdom legislation.
> 
> * All other information provided by you goes into a "public profile" and is entirely optional, all information held in that profile is held there at your own risk. This info is edited via your Control Panel in the forums.Content posted by you on the forum in threads and posts is entirely your responsibility (user).
> 
> * You have a legal right for the personal information held at [www.consumercourtforum.in](http://www.consumercourtforum.in/) to be updated if it is incorrect or deleted if you choose. Most of this can be done through your Control Panel in the forums. If you are having issues with this, please contact us if you need help.
> 
> * [www.consumercourtforum.in](http://www.consumercourtforum.in/) will take all reasonable effort to ensure that all personal information about you submitted is maintained secure on our server. However, we make no warranty to this.
> 
> * This site is intended for individuals over the age of 13. Any information collected is intended to be of individuals over the age of 13. According to COPPA, our site does NOT cater to children. "Operators of commercial websites or online services directed to children under 13 that collect personal information from children" require a COPPA agreement and privacy policy. Since we do not cater to this age group, no COPPA exists on [www.consumercourtforum.in](http://www.consumercourtforum.in/)
> 
> Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.  
>  Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to the users of this site based on their visit to this sites and/or other sites on the Internet.  
>  Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy ([Advertising and Privacy ? Google Privacy Center](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)).  
>  By using this website, you agree that both the web server, and any 3rd party we choose, such as advertising networks, may place a tracking cookie on your machine and access it at any time.
> 
> * This Privacy Policy may be modified at any time without notice. It is your responsibility to check this page for updates or changes. If you have any questions regarding yourprivacy, then Contact Us : [Consumer Court Forum - Contact Us](http://www.consumercourtforum.in/sendmessage.php)
> 
> *This website is meant for product and services reviews only and is not meant for personal comments about anyone. If we find any defamatory remarks we will delete those comments without warning. All posts are copyright thier respective posters and the views and comments belong to thier respective posters and in no way shall [Consumer Court Forum](http://www.consumercourtforum.in/) be held responsible for the content posted by users on this site.  
>  If you do not agree to all the above please do not use this website.
